Let's show up what we've got, Kaido. Huh?
The whole shebang.
We'll see how many survive.
Trafalgar!
Use your power!
Why aren't you teleporting
them downstairs?
If I could, I would have done it already.
Their Haki is too strong.
I can't get these two out of here.
In that case, we'll do it by force.
Damn it!
Here comes a big one!
Hope your stiff old joints
are still holding up.
Did you stretch?
I'll stretch that skin
off your skull, old man!
Conquest of the sea!
How the hell do you fight that?
We'll never dodge this.
Get away! Hurry!
Get out of here, Simmons!
You're gonna get off!
And...
Hurrah!
I can hear their voices.
They're around here somewhere.
I guess they got away.
They're better than I thought.
Hey, Saru.
You still alive?
I think so.
Nice job blocking that, even for a sack.
You saved us.
Where's Straw Hat? Ugh!
Kaido!
Red Hawk!
Hey, Kaido!
You moved!
Was it gonna hurt?
Ah!
Woo!
Let's go!
Thank you.
The End
There's a pile of explosives here, right?
Yes, I shall take them down.
The castle will burn to
the ground at this rate!
Screw you, Kaido!
And screw your new Onigashima
project too, dammit!
Orochi!
So, this is your doing, is it?
Look who crawled out
of their graves again!
I suppose you ghosts
are surprised to see me!
What exactly is your goal here?
It's been 20 years and you still
won't drop this blasted crusade!
You hunted me down!
All the way here!
Has your hate for me really
fueled you all this time?
Lord Orochi, it may be worth noting
that they didn't witness your execution.
Better to run.
I'll handle them.
Shut your mouth!
How dare you!
It looks like you took quite a beating.
Is that why you've come to me?
You're all half dead and you want
me to finish the job for you?
Or did somebody hit your heads too
hard and now you've lost your minds?
Step aside, Odochi.
We won't allow you to
waste any more of our time.
Then what happens if I say no? What?
Who the hell you think you
are looking down on me?
I'm the Shogun of the land of Wano!
You exist by my grace alone!
Stop at me, will you?
My actions have been
justified from the sky!
I had every right to take
revenge on the Kozuki clan!
what should have been mine!
Do you really think
you're the heroes here?
Citizens are supposed to
bow before their shogun,
not just from the peace Don't you
know the meaning of authority?
Flower shuriken!
This country oppressed me!
It deserves what it gets!
Don't look at me like that.
That silent judgment almost did it.
Stop it.
Don't look at me.
I'm the victim, don't you see?
Stop staring at me. No!
Lord Orochi!
I'll let them decide
your punishment in hell.
Onward!
Are you going to avenge your lord?
Seems you have some integrity after all.
Even though he was a fool, you
stayed loyal to him till the end.
Ironic hearing that
from you of all people.
But you and I are destined to fight!
I don't need vengeance as an excuse!
Wouldn't you agree, Race? Indeed!
Let's go!
Don't underestimate me, Brook!
Ah!
Back it up, lady!
I'll take you all on!
Go get him!
Pull it together!
Ready!
No!
Ah!
Oh, no!
Hmm!
Parker a free world!
It's time for us to take out the crash!
It's done. My turn. Now, roll.
Shambles.
Damn it, Zeus!
Can you do it, Roradoa?
Do I have a choice?
I won't let you go back to her!
Flame red!
Crossing the six pound!
No, no, no!
Stop the violence!
I'm just kidding, innocent guard!
Bobo, help me, please!
I'm coming!
Now's a chance!
Puck pistol, no! Oh!
Pathetic!
You thought you could win if
you took my homies away, huh?
I'll crush you!
Don't push it!
You're a pal!
In tact!
You idiot!
You think you'll beat me
by hitting me with a rock?
If there's no one to catch
her, then that's one down.
How was that?
Help me, Zos, where are you?
Where are you?
Don't you worry, I'm on my way!
Just wait one second, Mama!
That bastard's tough.
How is he standing?
That attack probably
broke half of his bones.
What is he made of?
Pathetic, Lin-Lin.
You got sloppy.
Guess I gotta do this job on my own.
Hey, Tyrant Hunter!
Let him go!
I'm warning you!
Time for shambles!
Injection shot!
I don't know what you did,
but I don't like it one bit.
Now die!
Anti-bacterial cart!
Oh!
Mama!
No way!
Hold on!
I'm coming!
Mama!
Pull it together, Drop!
That fire thing!
It's gonna save Big Mom if
we don't do something quick!
It doesn't matter. Let it go.
I don't want one of us to die.
I'd rather have the mission fail.
You don't have to worry!
All we had to do was tear
Big Mom and Kaido apart!
We've come far enough, no
need to throw your lives away.
I'll take care of Big Mom for you!
Oh, you saved me!
That sure was a close one, wasn't it?
Oh, my sweet, adorable Prometheus.
Thank you so much.
But somebody didn't bother.
Zeus, where the hell are you?
That useless idiot.
What a pity he really let
you down didn't he you can't
rely on that lazy chunk to
do anything if you ask me!
Yeah you're right.
I don't suppose I could ask for a favor.
Could I?
What is it?
That's funny.
Can you believe that face?
That cold stare.
Just like last time.
Even though he's unconscious,
the voice still glared at me.
You got something you want
to say, you little punk.
If you don't get up soon, I'm gonna
smash those eyeballs right in.
And then the rest of your skull.
And your face.
And your heart, too.
Hey, Traffy.
I got one good move left in me.
And it's going to push me to the limit.
You're kidding me.
Anything less than my
best wouldn't be enough.
It would just wear me down.
Either this attack works or I'd die.
Maybe it's just my time to go.
If this is it for me...
Good luck.
Hey, Kaido!
I got a duty to protect my captain.
You want to smash your head in that bad?
Try mine first, if you think you can!
Demon order!
Nine swords die out!
Ashura!
Blades drawn!
Nine swords dialed!
Ashwa, blade drawn!
Dead man's kill?
He cut me.
This breath so you have it as
well that was conquerors Haki.
Oh yeah you think that
means something to me
whatever you call it
it still wasn't enough.
That was all my strength and
you barely even flinched.
I was hoping you'd fall
to your knees, at least.
Well, you should be proud, kid.
You've given me a scar
that will never fade.
Your generation has
certainly earned its name.
Zoro, run! Hurry!
You stay right there.
Save yourself the trouble.
I'll come to you. Thunder!
Bawwa!
It's a damn shame.
If you'd join me, we could have
conquered the world together.
If we'd joined you, why the
hell would we ever join you?
We'll do anything to help the samurai.
I'll kick your ass no matter what!
You want to repeat that?
You'll kick my ass!
Alright, go ahead and try it then.
You're not the type to think
before you punch, are you?
If you've got something left, show me!
You need to pull back.
It's quite simple.
Haki, as you call it,
coats your entire body.
It can be used as invisible
armor or as a weapon.
And then, when you push beyond its limits,
your Haki doesn't simply
fortify your strength.
It penetrates the enemy's body
and destroys it from within.
Don't overstress yourself.
Let the Haki flow to your fist from
the parts that aren't using it.
All right!
The last time, it was too shallow.
In the midst of danger is
when true power blooms.
But I figured it out when
you attacked with your club.
You can infuse things
with Conqueror's Haki.
How exactly will knowing that help you?
You think you can do it too?
this is the privilege
of the strong a dead man
walking like you couldn't
dream of it i'll show you
Wow. Wow.
Don't overstress yourself!
Let the Haki flow through your fist
from the parts that aren't using it!
He didn't even touch her.
Zoro!
Traffy.
Thanks for protecting
me, but I'm good now.
You two should head downstairs.
I know I can do it.
I won't lose this time.
Tell everyone else.
We're gonna win!
Thank you.